oh this season was pretty good um
we accomplished a lot of goals made a
lot of history so extremely best to be a
part of this team and part of this
organization we did a lot of great
things
we fell short in both but it's part of
the game and it's going to help us grow
as players and hopefully the next time
we make it
we could be able to win
I think we just
did couldn't put 40 minutes of our type
of basketball up
you know um it's tough when you're
playing good teams
it's the people that can make the most
runs and the most important run and we
were just not able to do that
um
if we would have put up to 40 minutes
there's no down my mind we've been won
you know so um
just gotta figure out what we could do
better you know but um
for the most part I just don't think we
put the whole 40 minutes up of
the Oklahoma B card series basketball so
that's that's my reasoning why we came
up short and well we had the results
that we had
um
I feel like the main thing I've been
thinking is uh the team goals our team
goes and um just my teammates you know
my main thing was always to go out there
and fight hard for my teammates and um
we all had the same goal so it made me
want to go out there and go harder
because
I knew my teammates was going hard and
it was all competing for that same goal
so I feel like that's why that's what
made me you know what I'm saying play
the way I'm playing
pretty much yeah
um I feel like um the memorable game I
can't put in this one memorable game
because we made so much history this
year
and that would be hard for me to do I
just feel like this whole season for me
was very memorable for me because just
everything we did and how we just came
in and shocked everybody
we ain't shock ourselves we shocked
everybody else that really didn't
believe in US
um
so it's kind of hard but I always say
the emperor's cup was like just that
whole Emperor's cup that whole thing we
I feel like that was very memorable
um like I said when we beat brex I feel
like when we first beat breaks in the
beginning of the year we was just like
even in the preseason we tie with them
and then we beat we ended up beating
them
in our minds I felt like that was the
that was a point where we was like we
can be a really good team we could be
the best team in this league if we
wanted to if we just play our basketball
we could be the best team so
I would say well that was one of them
but I really can't give you one
or one moment that was the best because
I feel like this whole season was just
great
when my wife and my son decided to come
to my game right after like like a week
or so after they were like after she was
done pregnant being pregnant and stuff
so like maybe like that next month
she kind of surprised me by coming to
the game I don't remember what gaming
was but
I feel like that was the most memorable
for me because like she showed how
strong she was as a woman because I know
she was in a lot of pain but she wanted
to support me and
she knew how much that would have meant
to me and that meant a lot because I was
able my son was able to see me for the
first time playing basketball and
I knew she was in a lot of pain but she
just
she just show so much courage and you
know to decide to come out and watch me
play that that following game when I
knew she was in a lot of pain I just
that meant so much to me so that I feel
like that was uh when she the first game
she was able to come out I feel like
that was the most memorable game for me
um
I don't know if it was uh I don't
remember exactly when it was
um
I'm not sure but
it was the end of maybe the end of
December but I feel like that that game
that she came decided to come was the
most memorable for me though
I mean I guess I could stay in my career
high when I scored what 30 30 something
points uh I don't know I forgot who it
was against was it against Shibuya
I think it was Shibuya um I'll say just
my career high against Shibuya
was my former team so it was cool to
kick their butt and um
you know that was my career high so
that's a blessing um it was a fun game I
think Yuki we didn't I don't know I
don't think I think I was one of the
games Yuki was out so
it was kind of tough we didn't know what
to expect but we was able to go out
there and fight hard and get to Victory
still so that was that was like my most
memorable game stat wise
the best I love it here
um everybody here that's been helping me
from when I got here especially
when it comes to my child like they were
so open and they wanted to help me so
much especially ukd I really appreciate
you thank you for taking time out your
day even with training and
and just helping out with my wife
because that that really meant a lot to
me because you know I'm saying people
not often when you go overseas people
don't help you like that and to show
kind you being kind and just taking time
out your day when you didn't really have
to you know I'm saying you might have
other plans and you'll be able to do
that I really appreciate that KD that's
that's really I really love you for that
I thank you for that and and um
everybody else in the organization that
has been helping um me getting my son
together and making sure he's straight
and just welcoming me with open arms and
I just felt all the love this year from
from everybody so that's why I feel like
this is the best this is the best place
for me and
and I love to hear it this year for sure
so how do you got to design myself to
everybody in this organization who
helped me this year
all season I just want to spend time
with my family
um we'll be able to go home and
all my family's gonna meet my son for
the first time so it's going to be very
exciting
you know I haven't posted my son on
Instagram so I'm gonna be posting him on
Instagram soon so um
it's just a summer that I'm not going to
be able to forget because I'm going to
be able to
bring my son home to my family and my
wife's family and they're gonna finally
be able to meet him and he's not he
hasn't been to America yet so
he's a Japanese baby so it's like
I don't know I'm excited to how he going
how you're going to react and stuff like
that you know so I'm very excited for
that moment but I don't have no specific
plans but I'm just very excited to get
home to my family so I can meet my child
and my wife's family so I can meet him
as well
wow man the fast little boosters
it was such a blessing playing in front
of you guys this year
day in and day out game in and game out
you guys proved to be like some of the
best fans that I ever played in front of
you guys are amazing
y'all gave me so much energy this year
and
this team like we we I don't know where
we would have been without if it wasn't
for the boosters and the fans because
how much energy they gave especially
even in the away games they pulling up
to every game they're cheering their
butts off it was just amazing and I have
never really seen no fan base like that
so I'm very appreciative of the fans and
all the boosters for supporting us this
year and we really appreciate you guys